Preliminary Inventory to the Dumitru Danielopol Papers, 1940-1973
Hoover Institution Archives
- Soviet Union Seen in Throes of Deep Ideological Crisis, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 19, 1966
- Soviet Union Farm Policy Fails Again, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 5, 1969
- Soviet Union Farm Policy Fails Again, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 5, 1969
- Soviets Can't Hide the Truth Forever, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 24, 1972
- Soviets Use Soft Talk and Token Budget Cuts, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 17, 1964
- The Stalinist System Unable to Meet Romanian Crisis, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 3, 1970
- State Department Line Feared By Exile Group, The San Diego Union (Calif.), January 16, 1967
- Strain Showing - Reds Losing Yugoslavia, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), February 16, 1966
- Tales From the 'Workers Paradise', The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 13, 1966
- A Tax On Our Freedoms, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), February 15, 1968
- Telling It Like It Is, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), February 16, 1970
- Terror Present in Communist Land, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), December 8, 1966
- There is a Message for the World, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 11, 1972
- There's a Message in This Oscar, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 20, 1972
- They Don't Tick, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 18, 1969
- They'll Go 'Slumming' - Reds Seek Western Tourists, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 15, 1965
- Things Are Getting Worse For Soviet Man-in-the-Street, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 4, 1969
- A Threat to Survival of West, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 19, 1972
- Thrifty Danes Set Good Examples For World On How To Run Farms, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), September 22, 1966
- Time For President to Wake Up, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), September 17, 1966
- Tito Gets Warning, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), September 23, 1969
- Tito is Sitting on a Volcano, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 23, 1966
- Today's Success Story, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), June 13, 1970
- Too Many Native American Don't Appreciate Our Freedom, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 12, 1969
- Tourism Rough, One-Way Street in Red Countries, The San Diego Union (Calif.), January 3, 1967
- Trade Mission to Romania - Businessmen May Learn Truth, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 4, 1965
- Trade With the Communists, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), October 22, 1966
- Traditional American - Correct Label for U.S. Rootstock, The San Diego Union (Calif.) March 5, 1967
- Trial Balloon - Is Russian Danube Plan Aggression?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 23, 1964
- Tribute to Lenin Is Insult to Millions of His Victims, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 15, 1969
- Tribunal' Tactics Being Used To Embarrass United States, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 25, 1968
- A Tribute To Two Women, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), November 20, 1968
- The Russian Colors Again On Display, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 4, 1969
- Truth Faces Romania's Reds, Burbank Daily Review (Calif.), November 1, 1966
- Trying To Read In a Snowstorm, The Daily Journal (Wheaton, Illinois), October 19, 1972
- Tuning In On French Television, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 29, 1972
- Tunis Proves Good Tonic For American, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), June 4, 1967
- Two Veterans: Two Ideologies, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), August 23, 1972
- Ugly Americans At Home, Illinois State Journal, February 28, 1970
- The Uneducated 'New Left', The Sacramento Union (Calif.), January 25, 1970
- U.N. and the Mafia, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 4, 1969
- U.N. at New Low in Expediency, Monrovia Daily News-Post (Calif.), October 4, 1967
- U.N. Attention Strips Cloak From Rumania, The San Diego Union (Calif.), October 27, 1967
- U.N. Becomes a Major Issue, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 22, 1971
- United Nations Marks an Unhappy Birthday, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 9, 1966
- U.N. Proves Ineffectual in Malaysia Peace Try, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 24, 1964
- U.S. Allows Communists To Call Shots, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), January 15, 1968
- The U.S. and Greece, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), January 8, 1970
- U.S. Appeasement Aids Soviets, Monrovia Daily News-Post (Calif.), May 29, 1967
- United States Called Mandkind's Hope By Refugee From Romania, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), August 2, 1965
- U.S. Can Learn From French Vote, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 5, 1967
- United States Cannot Abandon Peoples of Captive Nations, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 6, 1967
- U.S. Embassy Protests Follow Same Pattern, The San Diego Union (Calif.), May 26, 1967
- U.S. Forces in Vietnam Know Why They're There, The San Diego Union (Calif.), November 22, 1967
- U.S. Fumbles in Closing Door To Stalin's Daughter, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 18, 1967
- The U.S. Gets Bad Name, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 23, 1971
- U.S. Headaches Echo in British Headlines, The San Diego Union (Calif.), April 27, 1970
- U.S. Helps Reds Solve Problems, Alhambra Post-Advocate (Calif.), March 21, 1967
- U.S. Image Abroad at New Low, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 11, 1968
- The U.S. Image of the Past, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), January 24, 1969
- U.S. in Third Phase of Longest War, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 11, 1966
- U.S. Isn't Selling Self in Europe, Illinois State Journal, September 15, 1966
- U.S. Link Vital to Western Pacific, The San Diego Union (Calif.), February 22, 1972
- U.S. May Lose Control of Free World Economy, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 17, 1970
- U.S. Protests, Ukrainia Mourns, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 22, 1969
- U.S. Seems to Be Importing (Commie) Ideas, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 3, 1968
- U.S. Trade Fails to Woo Romania From Moscow, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 27, 1964
- Unwillingness to Listen is World-Wide Malady, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 24, 1970
- The Upheaval in China, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), October 14, 1967
- Urges Nixon To Say Good Word For Martyred Romanians, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 25, 1969
- Victim of Success, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), January 19, 1970
- Victory For World Communism, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 12, 1966
- Vietnam Strategy Praised, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 8, 1972
- Vietnamese Vote Tells World They Would Rather Be Dead Than Red, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), September 19, 1966
- Vietniks Patriotic? Fulbright Seems to Think So, The San Diego Union (Calif.), May 6, 1966
- Voters To Remember Failures of Administration, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 24, 1964
- Washington 'Forgets' Red Murder, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 14, 1964
- We Can Not Escape Echoes of History, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), October 11, 1967
- We Must Keep Careful Watch For Covert Russian Actions, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 24, 1969
- We Still Kick Our Friends, Aid Our Enemies, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), August 7, 1967
- West German Campus is Pleasant Sight, The San Diego Union (Calif.) May 22, 1967
- West Warned On Aid to Reds, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 18, 1964
- What Else is New? Pattern of Concession Familiar to Communism South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), June 25, 1969
- What Kind of Democracy?, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), June 28, 1968
- What LBJ Didn't Tell Them, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 21, 1966
- Where Do Jews Stand Today in Soviet Union?, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 6, 1967
- Where Has U Thant Been?, Burbank Daily Review (Calif.), January 26, 1967
- Where Is Angela's Logic?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 13, 1972
- Who Really Pays?, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), December 29, 1969
- Why Do We Supply Our Foes With Ammunition For War?, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 3, 1967
- Why Is Jackie Going To Cambodia?, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), October 13, 1967
- Why Is Johnson Silent On Policy Toward Reds?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 10, 1964
- Will Captive Nations Fare Better With LBJ?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), November 26, 1964
- Will Free World Punish the Communist Criminals?, The San Diego (Calif.), October 24, 1965
- Will New 'Crisis' Precede Election?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 4, 1964
- Will President Use Gimmick To Aid Humphrey's Campaign?, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), October 28, 1968
- Will Reds March Again?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 15, 1970
- Wishful Thinking Dominates Our Relations With Reds, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 22, 1968
- A World On Aggression, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 20, 1969
- Work Shortage - Population Lag Has Russ In a Quandary, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), October 3, 1969
- Worker's Paradise Target of Iron Curtain Jokesters, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 21, 1967
- World Needs Great Food Source, The San Diego Union (Calif.), October 9, 1972
- World Sees How Fragile Is the Communist System, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), June 22, 1967
- You Can't Believe the Russians, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 2, 1967
- You Can't Fool Them All - Attitude of Youth Worries Reds, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 23, 1965